<!--
  ~ MIT License
  ~
  ~ Copyright (c) 2016 - 2018 Luke Myers (FRC Team 980 ThunderBots)
  ~
  ~ Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
  ~ of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal
  ~ in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
  ~ to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
  ~ copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
  ~ furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:
  ~
  ~ The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all
  ~ copies or substantial portions of the Software.
  ~
  ~ THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
  ~ IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
  ~ FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
  ~ AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
  ~ LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
  ~ OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE
  ~ SOFTWARE.
  -->

<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ThunderScout</string>

    <string name="welcome_message">
        ThunderScout is Team 980\'s robust and intuitive scouting app for FIRST Robotics Competition teams. Scout and analyze matches with an intuitive interface, and modularly configure and link devices to match the structure of your scouting team.
        \n
        \nTo get started, configure your device in the app settings, or dive in and scout your first match!
    </string>

    <string name="telemetry_prompt">
        ThunderScout uses Firebase Analytics to collect information such as usage statistics and crash reports.
        \n
        \nThis information is used to provide insight on app performance as well as fix bugs for future releases.
        \n
        \nYou can opt out of telemetry in the app settings.
    </string>

    <!--- TODO Last update: v17 -->
    <string name="update_notes">
        Introducing ThunderCloud! With ThunderCloud, your data gains an additional home on Google\'s Firebase cloud servers.
        \nSigning in with an email or Google account allows you to store data online, separately from what\'s already saved on your local device.
        \nThis data can then be viewed on other devices signed in to ThunderScout with this account.
        \n
        \nThunderCloud is still in its infancy, and much of its design is not final - so your feedback would be very much appreciated!
        \n
        \n(Oh, and the team info screen now incorporates individual match tabs.)
        \n
        \nTechnical note: ThunderCloud is being in a separate branch from the rest of the app, and may change significantly or disappear in subsequent releases.
        </string>

    <!--- TODO remove before flight (stable) -->
    <string name="thundercloud_disclaimer">
        ThunderCloud is currently in beta. No guarantees are made as to the preservation of your data.
        \n
        \nIt is recommenced to use ThunderCloud while online. Offline caching has not been tested, and may not work as intended.
        \n
        \nA server wipe is not expected until after the Houston Championship. Make sure to backup your data locally during and after the event.
        \n
        \nThunderCloud is not guaranteed to ship with the 2018.2 release, and may change significantly in future releases.
        \n
        \nFor more information, please contact the developer at info@team980.com.</string>

    <string-array name="alliance_stations_array">
        <item>Red 1</item>
        <item>Red 2</item>
        <item>Red 3</item>
        <item>Blue 1</item>
        <item>Blue 2</item>
        <item>Blue 3</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="climbing_stats_array">
        <item>DID NOT CLIMB</item>
        <item>ATTEMPTED CLIMB</item>
        <item>CLIMBED</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="iexport_file_types">
        <item>CSV</item>
        <!--<item>JSON</item>-->
    </string-array>

    <string name="shortcut_match_scout_short">Match scout</string>
    <string name="shortcut_match_scout_long">Scout a match</string>
    <string name="shortcut_toggle_bluetooth_server_short">Toggle server</string>
    <string name="shortcut_toggle_bluetooth_server_long">Toggle Bluetooth Server</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="fui_default_toolbar_title" translatable="false">ThunderCloud</string>
</resources>
