<!--
  ~ MIT License
  ~
  ~ Copyright (c) 2016 - 2018 Luke Myers (FRC Team 980 ThunderBots)
  ~
  ~ Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
  ~ of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal
  ~ in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
  ~ to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
  ~ copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
  ~ furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:
  ~
  ~ The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all
  ~ copies or substantial portions of the Software.
  ~
  ~ THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
  ~ IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
  ~ FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
  ~ AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
  ~ LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
  ~ OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE
  ~ SOFTWARE.
  -->

<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ThunderScout</string>

    <string name="welcome_message">
        ThunderScout is designed by FRC Team 980 ThunderBots to help you scout matches quickly and powerfully.
        With an intuitively designed scouting flow, robust configuration framework, and intelligent data presentation,
        ThunderScout can adapt to fit any team\'s needs.
        \n
        \nTo get started, configure your device in the app settings, or dive in and scout your first match!
    </string>

    <string name="telemetry_prompt">
        ThunderScout uses Firebase Analytics to collect information such as usage statistics and crash reports.
        \n
        \nThis information is used to provide insight on app performance as well as fix bugs for future releases.
        \n
        \nYou can opt out of telemetry in the app settings.
    </string>

    <!--- TODO Last update: v15 -->
    <string name="update_notes">
        ThunderScout 2.0 is a major update that provides key improvements to the analytic features and the Bluetooth transfer system.
        \n
        \nThunderScout\'s analytic features have been redesigned from the ground up to be more useful, relevant, and elegant:
        \n• The data collected is now presented across multiple screens.
        \n• The Matches screen displays a generated schedule of the event, allowing you to see at a glance all the data you have collected, or may be missing.
        \n• The Rankings screen ranks teams by an estimation of how many points they would score, on average, alone on the field based on your collected data.
        \n• Both these screens are searchable, and you can customize the ranking criteria for the latter.
        \n
        \nThe match and team breakdowns have been updated to highlight statistical performance and point estimations, and now take up less space.
        \n• A third "alliance" comparison view is also visible when you select three teams on the Rankings screen.
        \n
        \nThe Bluetooth transfer system has been improved to be more reliable and actionable:
        \n• Notifications now keep you informed with the progress of background transfers and allow you to edit and retry failed transfers.
        \n• The backend implementation has also been improved with variable alliance•station-based delays, automatic reattempts, and a confirmation phase.
        \n• You can also select matches on either the Matches or the Rankings screen and batch send them to a specified device.
        \n
        \nOther notable changes:
        \n• The alliance field has been updated to reflect individual alliance stations.
        \n• The Bluetooth Device selection preference now opens a system dialog.
        \n• An app shortcut (requires Android 7.1 and/or a supporting launcher) has been added to toggle the Bluetooth server.
        \n• New squircle icon (now Adaptive on Android Oreo)
        \n• You can now opt out of telemetry in the settings
        \n• These patch notes are also accessible from the About menu, if you ever go looking for them
    </string>

    <string-array name="alliance_stations_array">
        <item>Red 1</item>
        <item>Red 2</item>
        <item>Red 3</item>
        <item>Blue 1</item>
        <item>Blue 2</item>
        <item>Blue 3</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="climbing_stats_array">
        <item>Did not climb</item>
        <item>Attempted climb</item>
        <item>Climbed</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="iexport_file_types">
        <item>CSV</item>
        <!--<item>JSON</item>-->
    </string-array>

    <string name="shortcut_match_scout_short">Match scout</string>
    <string name="shortcut_match_scout_long">Scout a match</string>
    <string name="shortcut_toggle_bluetooth_server_short">Toggle server</string>
    <string name="shortcut_toggle_bluetooth_server_long">Toggle Bluetooth Server</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
</resources>
